A Guide to the Papers of William B. Spong, 1965-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Federal Files
  - Executive Branch
    - Executive Office of the President - Economic Opportunity, Office of 1972 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Emergency Food and Medical Supplies 1972 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Federal Maritime Commission 1971 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - National Security 1971 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Office of Emergency Preparedness 1971 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Office of Management and Budget 1971-1972 (Box 107)
    - Executive Office of the President - Office of Management and Budget - Grade Escalation 1972 (Box 107)
    - Executive Office of the President - Pay Board 1972 (Box 107)
    - Executive Office of the President - Price Commission 1972 (Box 107)
    - Executive Office of the President - Robert F. Kennedy Gravesite 1969 (Box 107)
    - Executive Office of the President - Special Representative for Trade Negotiations 1967-1969 (Box 107)
    - Executive Office of the President - White House Fellowships 1969-1970 (Box 107)
    - Federal Coal Mine Safety Commission 1967 (Box 107)
    - Federal Communications Commission 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 107)
    - Federal Communications Commission - Cable T.V. 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 107)
    - Federal Communications Commission - Fairness Doctrine 1967-1968 (Box 107)
    - Federal Communications Commission - Obscenity & Violence 1968-1972 (Box 107)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Commission 1967-1971 (Box 107)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board 1967-1972 (Box 107)
    - Federal Maritime Commission 1969-1972 (Box 107)
    - Federal Mediation & Conciliation Service 1969 (Box 107)
    - Federal Power Commission 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 107)
    - Federal Power Commission - Blue Ridge Project 1967-1972, n.d., 11 folders (Box 108)
    - Federal Power Commission - Danville Power Dispute 1969-1970 (Box 108)
    - Federal Power Commission - Marble Valley Project 1968-1971, 2 folders (Box 108)
    - Federal Power Commission - Natural Gas Supply 1970 (Box 108)
    - Federal Power Commission - North Anna Project 1968-1970 (Box 108)
    - Federal Reserve System 1967-1972 (Box 108)
    - Federal Reserve System - Regulation "Z" 1969-1970 (Box 108)
    - Federal Trade Commission 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 108)
    - Federal Trade Commission - Georgia Pacific Company 1971-1972 (Box 108)
    - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission 1967-1970 (Box 108)
    - General Services Administration 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - Barracks "K" Property, Arlington County 1970-1972 (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - [Old] Coast Guard Station, Virginia Beach 1971 (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - Credit Unions in Federal Buildings 1971 (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - Guard in Post Office Building, Abingdon, Virginia 1971 (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - Norfolk Area Office Space 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - Social Security Buildings 1971-1972 (Box 109)
    - General Services Administration - Surplus Property 1971-1972 (Box 109)
    - Health, Education & Welfare [HEW] 1968-1972, 5 folders (Box 109)
    - HEW - Charlottesville - Regional Office Relocation 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 109)
    - HEW - Civil Rights 1971-1972 (Box 109)
    - HEW - Civil Rights - Sexual Discrimination - Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1972 (Box 109)
    - HEW - Education 1967-1970, 5 folders (Box 109)
    - HEW - Education 1971-1972, 7 folders (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Black Secondary Principals 1970-1971 (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Colonel Hassan Jeru-Ahmed - Blackman's Development Center 1971-1972 (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Desegregation 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Desegregation - Accomack County through Newport News School 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Desegregation - Norfolk 1969-1970 (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Desegregation - Norfolk & Portsmouth School Cases 1969 May-Jun, 2 folders (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Desegregation - Portsmouth School 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Desegregation - Southampton County- Suffolk County 1969 & 1971 (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Elementary & Secondary 1967-1970, 3 folders (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Elementary & Secondary - Funding 1967 Dec - 1968 (Box 110)
    - HEW - Education - Elementary & Secondary - Environmental Education Act 1971 Feb-Jun, 2 folders (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Headstart 1970-1971 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Higher 1967-1971, 3 folders (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Higher - Chesapeake College Accreditation 1970 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Higher - Funding & Grants 1968-1971 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Higher - Reid, James Reuben 1968 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Library Services & Construction 1971 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Sex 1969 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Special Services Program 1971 Apr-May, 2 folders (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Student Loans 1970 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Education - Vocational & Rehabilitation 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 111)
    - HEW - Food & Drug Administration 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 111)
    - HEW - Food & Drug Administration - Combination Drugs Regulation 1971 Mar-May, 2 folders (Box 111)
    - HEW - Food & Drug Administration - DES in Beef Cattle 1971 Aug-1972 Sep (Box 111)
    - HEW - Food & Drug Administration - Fair Labeling & Packaging Act 1969 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Food & Drug Administration - Milk Imports 1968 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Food & Drug Administration - Peanut Container Standards 1970 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Health 1971-1972 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Health - Central State Hospital, Petersburg and Retardation 1971 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Health - Funding 1970-1971 (Box 111)
    - HEW - Health - Migrant Hospitalization 1972 (Box 112)
    - HEW - Health - Patrick County Hospital 1971 (Box 112)
    - HEW - Health - Proposed Charity Regulations 1972 May-Aug, 2 folders (Box 112)
    - HEW - Medical Schools 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 112)
    - HEW - National Air Pollution Control Administration 1968-1970 (Box 112)
    - HEW - National Institute of Health 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 112)
    - HEW - National Institute of Mental Health 1972 (Box 112)
    - HEW - National Institute of Mental Health - Portsmouth Narcotic Addicts Rehabilitation Center Organization 1971-1972 (Box 112)
    - HEW - Public Health Service 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 112)
    - HEW - Public Health Service - Combined Antibiotics 1969 (Box 112)
    - HEW - Public Health Service - Grants & Funding 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 112)
    - HEW - Public Health Service - Hospitals 1969-1972, 5 folders (Box 112)
    - HEW - Public Health Service - Hospitals - Norfolk Area Medical Center Authority Operations Proposal 1971 (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social & Rehabilitation Service 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social & Rehabilitation Service - Social Work & Social Education Funds 1971 (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social Security Administration 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social Security Administration - Black Lung Program 1970-1972, 4 folders (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social Security Administration - Hearing Examiners 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social Security Administration - Hearing Examiners - Professor Viles Report 1972 (Box 113)
    - HEW - Social Security Administration - Medicare 1968-1972 (Box 113)
    - HEW - Welfare Administration 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 113)
    - HEW - Welfare Administration - Franklin County 1969-1970 (Box 113)
    - Housing & Urban Development 1967-1972, 10 folders (Box 114)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Audits & Investigations 1970-1971 (Box 114)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Development & Renewal 1972 (Box 114)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Development & Renewal - Charlottesville through Wytheville 1969-1972, 6 folders (Box 114)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Federal Housing Administration 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Flood Insurance 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Home Builders Association 1970-1972 (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Housing Programs 1970-1972 (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Model Cities 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Nursing & Retirement Homes - Annandale through Roanoke 1969-1972 (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Operation Breakthrough 1969-1970 (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Planning Commissions 1967-1968 (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Summer Youth Program 1971 (Box 115)
    - Housing & Urban Development - Water & Sewage - Alleghany County through Waterford 1968-1972 (Box 115)
    - Indian Claims Administration 1968 (Box 115)
    - Interior 1967-1972 Aug, 13 folders (Box 115)
    - Interior 1972 Sep-Nov (Box 116)
    - Interior - Alaska Pipeline 1970 (Box 116)
    - Interior - Assateague 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Interior - Back Bay 1970-1972, 7 folders (Box 116)
    - Interior - Endangered Species 1970-1971 (Box 116)
    - Interior - Fish & Wildlife Service 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 116)
    - Interior - Fish & Wildlife Service - Fish Applications 1970-1971 (Box 116)
    - Interior - Funding Program 1966-1973 (Box 116)
    - Interior - Geological Survey 1967-1972 (Box 116)
    - Interior - Hickel Appointment 1969, 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Interior - Hunting Creek 1968-1971 (Box 116)
    - Interior - Indian Affairs, Bureau of 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 117)
    - Interior - Job Information 1968-1970 (Box 117)
    - Interior - Land Management, Bureau of 1968-1972 (Box 117)
    - Interior - Mines, Bureau of 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 117)
    - Interior - Mines, Bureau of - Coal Shortage 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 117)
    - Interior - Mines, Bureau of - Mine Safety 1969-1971, 5 folders (Box 117)
    - Interior - Mount Vernon View 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 117)
    - Interior - National Park Service 1967-1968, 4 folders (Box 117)
    - Interior - National Park Service 1969-1972, 8 folders (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Alexandria 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Bicycle Trails 1968-1972 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Blue Ridge Parkway 1968-1970 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Cape Hatteras 1967-1969 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Cumberland Gap 1967-1969 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Dismal Swamp 1969-1970 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Ferry Farm 1971-1972 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Jefferson Memorial 1970 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Prince William Park 1971 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Offshore Islands 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Outdoor Recreation, Bureau of 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Reclamation, Bureau of 1967-1970 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Richmond Move 1971 (Box 118)
    - Interior - National Park Service - Seals 1969-1970 (Box 118)
    - Interior - Shenandoah National Park 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Interior - Water Pollution Control Administration 1967-1970, 7 folders (Box 119)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 119)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission - Boxcar Shortage 1969-1970 (Box 119)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission - Concealed Damages 1969-1970 (Box 119)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission - Train Discontinuance 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission - Train Discontinuance 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Justice 1967-1972, 9 folders (Box 120)
    - Justice - Carmichael, Stokley 1968 (Box 120)
    - Justice - Federal Bureau of Investigation 1967-1972 (Box 120)
    - Justice - Gun Control 1968 (Box 120)
    - Justice - Immigration & Naturalization Service 1967-1972 (Box 120)
    - Justice - Law Enforcement Education Program 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Justice - Narcotics, Bureau of 1969-1971 (Box 120)
    - Labor 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Labor 1969-1972, 6 folders (Box 121)
    - Labor - Employees Compensation, Bureau of 1967-1971 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Glade Spring Community Center 1969 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Green Thumb Project 1969-1972 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Manpower Development & Training 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Labor - Neighborhood Youth Corps 1967-1972 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Railroad Strike 1970 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Spanish Speaking People of Virginia 1970-1972 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Summer Youth Programs 1971-1972 (Box 121)
    - Labor - Wage Rates 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 121)
    - National Academy of Science 1972 (Box 121)
    - National Aeronautics & Space Administration 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 121)
    - National Aeronautics & Space Administration - Conversion/Night Shift 1972 (Box 121)
    - National Aeronautics & Space Administration - Space Launch 1970-1972 (Box 121)
    - National Capital Housing Authority 1969 (Box 121)
    - National Commission on Product Safety 1969-1970 (Box 121)
    - National Endowment for the Arts & Humanities 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 121)
    - National Labor Relations Board 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 122)
    - National Mediation Board 1967-1970 (Box 122)
    - National Science Foundation 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 122)
    - National Science Foundation - Chesapeake Bay 1971 (Box 122)
    - Post Office 1967-1972, 17 folders (Box 122)
    - Post Office - Annandale Post Office Employee Dispute 1970-1972 (Box 122)
    - Post Office - Commemorative Stamp Recommendations 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Commemorative Stamp Recommendations - Naval Shipyard 1967, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Complaints 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Jobs 1967-1970 (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Mobile Unit 1967 (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Obscene Mail 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Postmarks 1967-1969 (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Rates 1969-1972 (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Unicef Sales 1970 (Box 123)
    - Post Office - Zip Codes 1967-1968 (Box 123)
    - Public Land Law Review Commission 1968 (Box 123)
    - Railroad Retirement Board 1967-1972 (Box 123)
    - Securities & Exchange Commission 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Selective Service 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Selective Service - Consolidation of Offices 1971 (Box 123)
    - Selective Service - Draft Cards 1971 (Box 123)
    - Selective Service - Draft Deferments 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Selective Service - Lottery System 1972 (Box 124)
    - Selective Service - Volunteer Army 1969-1971 (Box 124)
    - Small Business Administration 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 124)
    - Small Business Administration - Loan Applications 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Small Business Administration - Pier One Restaurant 1970-1972 (Box 124)
    - Smithsonian Institute 1967-1972 (Box 124)
    - State Department 1967-1971, 13 folders (Box 124)
    - State Department 1972, 3 folders (Box 125)
    - State - Africa 1969-1971 (Box 125)
    - State - Agency for International Development 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - State - Briefings 1969-1971, 7 folders (Box 125)
    - State - Carmichael, Stokely 1968 (Box 125)
    - State - Cuba 1970-1972 (Box 125)
    - State - Employment 1971 (Box 125)
    - State - Hijackings 1968-1970 (Box 125)
    - State - Middle East 1970 (Box 125)
    - State - Offshore Fishing 1968-1972, 6 folders (Box 125)
    - State - Passports 1970-1971 (Box 125)
    - State - Peace Corps 1967-1970 (Box 126)
    - State - Radio Free Europe 1972 (Box 126)
    - State - Rough Notes 1969-1970 (Box 126)
    - State - Soviet Jews 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 126)
    - State - United Nations 1970-1972 (Box 126)
    - State - Vietnam 1968-1971, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Subversive Action Control Board 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Subversive Action Control Board - Simon McHugh Appointment 1967 (Box 126)
    - Tariff Commission 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 126)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority 1968-1972 (Box 126)
    - Transportation 1968-1972, 8 folders (Box 126)
    - Transportation - Amtrak 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Transportation - Coast Guard 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 127)
    - Transportation - Coast Guard - Closing of Stations 1971-1972 (Box 127)
    - Transportation - Coast Guard - Lithuanian Defector Incident 1970 (Box 127)
    - Transportation - Federal Aviation Administration [F.A.A.] 1967-1972, 12 folders (Box 127)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Air Traffic Controllers 1969-1970 (Box 127)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Chesterfield Airport 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Dulles Airport 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Flight Restrictions 1968-1969, 3 folders (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Fort Story Airport 1968 (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Lonesome Pine Airport 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - National Airport 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Sale of Dulles & National Airports 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Sonic Booms 1968-1970 (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Stretch Jets 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - Travel Clubs 1967 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.A.A. - User Charges 1967 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - Federal Highway Administration [F.H.A.] 1967-1972, 7 folders (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F. H. A. - Dulles Access Road 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Equal Employment 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Fund Withholding 1968 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Highway Beautification 1967-1971 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Interstate 95 1967 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Public Roads, Bureau of 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Public Roads, Bureau of - Portsmouth Interchange 1968-1970 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Public Roads, Bureau of - Public Hearings 1968-1969 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Public Roads, Bureau of - Route 7 1967 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - F.H.A. - Three Sisters Bridge 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 129)
    - Transportation - Merchant Marines 1967-1972 (Box 129)
    - Transportation - National Highway Safety Bureau 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - Transportation - National Highway Traffic Safety Administration 1968-1972, 4 folders (Box 130)
    - Transportation - National Traffic Safety Board 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 130)
    - Transportation - Railpax 1970-1971, 4 folders (Box 130)
    - Transportation - Rapid Transit 1967-1971 (Box 130)
    - Transportation Tire Identification & Record Keeping 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 130)
    - Treasury 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 130)
    - Treasury - Alcohol, Firearms & Tobacco 1968-1969 (Box 130)
    - Treasury - Atlantic National Bank - Bi-Racial Bank 1970 (Box 130)
    - Treasury - Candidacy for Treasurer - Hogg, George 1967 (Box 130)
    - Treasury - Customs Bureau 1969-1972 (Box 130)
    - Treasury - Internal Revenue Service 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 130)
    - Treasury - Internal Revenue Service 1969-1972, 7 folders (Box 131)
    - Treasury - Internal Revenue Service - Institutional Exemptions - Broadwater Academy - Isle of Wight Educational Foundation 1967-1969 (Box 131)
    - Treasury - Internal Revenue Service - Institutional Exemptions - Lonsdale Corporations - Virginia Academy of Science 1967 (Box 131)
    - Treasury - Internal Revenue Service - Taxation of Military Moving Allowance 1970 Nov-1971 Jul (Box 131)
    - Treasury - Savings Bonds Division 1967 Dec - 1970 Apr (Box 131)
    - Treasury - Savings Bonds Division - Appointments 1967 (Box 131)
    - United States Information Agency 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - United States Information Agency - Funding 1972 (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Broida Newsletter 1970-1971 (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Hospitals 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Hospitals - Hampton Hospital 1969-1972 (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Hospitals - McGuire Hospital 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Hospitals - Roanoke/Salem Hospital 1971-1972 (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Regionalization in Virginia 1971 (Box 131)
    - Veterans Administration - Roanoke Regional Office 1971 (Box 131)
    - Water Resources Council 1969 (Box 131)
    - White House Announcements 1967 (Box 131)
  - Judicial Branch
    - Administrative Office of the Courts 1967-1970 (Box 132)
    - Nomination of Judges 1967-1971, 6 folders (Box 132)
    - Supreme Court 1966-1971 (Box 132)
    - Supreme Court - Charlotte-Mecklenburg School Case 1970-1971 (Box 132)
    - United States Court of Claims 1967-1968 (Box 132)
  - Legislative Branch
    - Architect of the Capitol 1967-1971 (Box 132)
    - Congress 1967-1971 (Box 132)
    - Congress - House of Representatives 1967-1968 (Box 132)
    - Congress - House of Representatives - Powell, Adam Clayton 1967 & 1969 (Box 132)
    - Congress - Senate 1967-1971 (Box 132)
    - General Accounting Office 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 132)
    - General Accounting Office - Procurement 1968-1972 (Box 132)
    - General Accounting Office - Reports 1971 (Box 132)
    - Government Printing Office 1967-1972 (Box 132)
    - Library of Congress 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Casework Files
    - Casework Files (Alphabetical Arrangement by Organization)
      - Civil Service Commission Casework Files A-Z 1967, 7 folders (Box 132 (CONT.))
      - Civil Service Commission Casework Files A-Z 1968, 6 folders (Box 133)
      - Commerce Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968 (Box 133)
      - Defense Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968 (Box 133)
      - Defense - Air Force Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 4 folders (Box 133)
      - Defense - Army Casework Files A-Z 1967, 7 folders (Box 133)
      - Defense - Army Casework Files A-Cl 1968, 2 folders (Box 133)
      - Defense - Army Casework Files Co-Z 1968, 9 folders (Box 134)
      - Defense - Marines Casework Files A-Z 1968, 2 folders (Box 134)
      - Defense - Navy Casework Files A-Z 1967, 6 folders (Box 134)
      - Defense - Navy Casework Files A-H 1968, 6 folders (Box 134)
      - Defense - Navy Casework Files J-Z 1968, 4 folders (Box 135)
      - District of Columbia Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968 (Box 135)
      - Economic Opportunity, Office of Casework Files A-Z 1968-1970 (Box 135)
      - General Accounting Office Casework Files A-Z 1968 (Box 135)
      - General Services Administration Casework Files A-Z 1968 (Box 135)
      - Health, Education & Welfare Casework Files A-Z ca. 1967-1972, 13 folders (Box 135)
      - Housing and Urban Development Casework Files A-Z ca. 1967-1972 (Box 135)
      - Justice Casework Files A-Z 1967 (Box 135)
      - Justice Casework Files A-Z 1968, 4 folders (Box 136)
      - Labor Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - Post Office Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 4 folders (Box 136)
      - Selective Service Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 136)
      - Small Business Administration A-Z 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 136)
      - State Department Casework Files A-Z 1967-1968, 7 folders (Box 136)